# **Christine Kiyabu**

## **UI** Designer

https://christinek2.github.io/portfolio-website/

Los Angeles, CA

#### **Contact Details**

christine.s.kiyabu@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/christinese-k Languages: English & Japanese

### **PROFILE**

Accurately assesses individual's needs and creates aesthetically functional UI design by combining both the fascination for the human response with an eye for creativity.

Diverse background, ranging from a psychology degree and experience in sales strategy, to a creative and visual design-focused background in cosmetology and wedding planning.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### UI/UX Design Certificate | 2020

CareerFoundry

- 10 month/500+ hours intensive project-based training program with industry-leading mentors. Studies spanned from visual design principles, color theory, grids, and UI/UX best practices to wireframing, prototyping, responsive design, mobile gestures, and animated interactions.
- Student Projects https://christinek2.github.io/portfolio-website/
  Unfiltered You: iOS Mobile Online Skincare Product Store App
  TrackHere: iOS & Android Mobile Package Tracking Aggregator App
  Designed an iOS mobile app for a skincare product store through the process of competitor analysis, user flows, user testing, iteration, branding, wireframing, and prototyping.

#### Cosmetology License | 2015

KC Beauty Academy

#### BA Psychology | 2012

University of California, Santa Barbara

## **TOOLS**

- Sketch
- Photoshop
- InVision
- Marvel
- Flinto
- Balsamiq
- GitHub
- Atom
- UsabilitvHub
- Microsoft Office

## DESIGN SKILLS

- Web & Mobile Design
- Wireframing
- Branding/Visual Design
- Usability & A/B Testing
- Storytelling
- User Research
- User Flows
- User Personas
- Style Guides
- Prototyping

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Sales Strategy Administrative Assistant** | Apr 2018 - Present Wismettac Asian Foods Inc (Santa Fe Springs, CA)

- Increase customer acquisition and brand awareness through the creation of marketing materials such as sell sheets, brochures, trade show materials, packages
- Conduct market research to identify and analyze consumer behavior

#### **Behavioral Therapist** | May 2016 - May 2017 Center for Autism & Related Disorders (Los Angeles, CA)

• Implemented behavioral intervention programs to prompt interactive success

## Bridal Hair & Makeup Artist | Jan 2016 - May 2017

Kelly Zhang Studio (Pasadena, CA)

• Performed professional bridal makeup on 150+ clients

## Wedding Planner | Jul 2013 - Nov 2013

Kanalu Wedding (Honolulu, HI)

 Multi-tasked to organize and plan every aspect of client weddings, from creating financial estimates to coordinating with multiple vendors